vvnyk.com 2015-05-21

# Privacy Policy

vvnyk.com respect and protect the use of the global user privacy. "Privacy" refers to personally identifiable information that you provide to vvnyk.com, including user registration information in the name of a valid personal ID number, contact information, home address and other user information when you register vvnyk.com services. In order to provide more timely, accurate, convenient and personalized service, vvnyk.com use and disclosure of user information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Meanwhile, vvnyk.com will be a high degree of conscientiousness obligation to treat user information. This Privacy Policy vvnyk.com user services are an integral part of the agreement. vvnyk.com before using the service provided, please read the following user privacy policy carefully.

vvnyk.com to provide users with personal registration information for absolute control over all the information provided by the user at the time of registration, are based on voluntary, users have the right at any time to refuse to provide such information. Users can use the "Modify Personal Information" to view or modify personal information。

**Users of Information Security**

vvnyk.com the information provided by the user will be strict management and protection, vvnyk.com through technical means to provide privacy protection services, strengthen internal management and other measures to fully protect the security of personal information of users. Meanwhile, vvnyk.com through to the other server backup, user password encryption and other security measures to ensure that user information is not lost as much as possible, not be abused or altered. Notwithstanding the foregoing, security measures must be taken not to prompt the user exists in the information network "perfect security measures"。

**User Information Disclosure**

vvnyk.com promise not to publicly or provide personal information to a third party registered users, including non-disclosure of the service users in the use of storage, with the following exceptions：

1, According to the relevant laws and regulations;

2, In accordance with the requirements of the relevant government departments;

3, Maintenance of the individual and public safety community;

4, The need to safeguard public interests;

5, Safeguard the legitimate rights and interests of the site;

6, Obtain prior express authorization of users;

7, Meet other related requirements;

**Use of Cookies technology**

1, Cookies refers to a technique, when a user visits has vvnyk.com Cookies device, vvnyk.com the server will automatically send Cookies to the user's browser, and stored in a user's computer hard drive, which will be responsible for Cookies the user later visits vvnyk.com record various activities, personal information, browsing habits, consumption habits.

2, The use of Cookies technology, vvnyk.com able to provide users with more detailed personalized service. Do not have to re-enter the password every time vvnyk.com will use Cookies Interrupted your reading preferences, thereby providing information of interest to the user data or to save your password so that the user visits vvnyk.com.

vvnyk.com may be modified from time to time in our Privacy Policy, these changes will be reflected in this policy. Any modification to the legality of user satisfaction and policies put in an important position. vvnyk.com encourage users each time the page is accessed vvnyk.com review our Privacy Policy. Privacy policy about vvnyk.com have any comments or suggestions, please call, fax or e-mail direct contact with vvnyk.com Customer Service.
